[{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678948772,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":20853,"timeElapsed":110039},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678956516,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":7741,"timeElapsed":117784},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678965510,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":8990,"timeElapsed":126777},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678976590,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":11077,"timeElapsed":137858},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678985624,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":9030,"timeElapsed":146891},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678995873,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":10245,"timeElapsed":157141},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679003569,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":7692,"timeElapsed":164836},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679008354,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":4783,"timeElapsed":169622},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679015350,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":6993,"timeElapsed":176618},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679026446,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":7170,"timeElapsed":187713},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679033493,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":7045,"timeElapsed":194761},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679044551,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":11055,"timeElapsed":205819},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679049197,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":4643,"timeElapsed":210465},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679067089,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":17891,"timeElapsed":228357},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679072087,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":4995,"timeElapsed":233355},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679080271,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":8182,"timeElapsed":241539},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679085315,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":5042,"timeElapsed":246583},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679090211,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"136","question":"If you had to move away from your current home town or city, where would you go, and what would you miss most about where you currently live?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":4894,"timeElapsed":251479},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679097741,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":5398,"timeElapsed":259008},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679101587,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3844,"timeElapsed":262855},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679108214,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":6626,"timeElapsed":269482},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679113318,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":5102,"timeElapsed":274586},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679121988,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":8668,"timeElapsed":283256},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679129720,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":7729,"timeElapsed":290988},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679135195,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":5473,"timeElapsed":296463},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679138501,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":3304,"timeElapsed":299769},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679142644,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":4141,"timeElapsed":303912},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679159910,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":17264,"timeElapsed":321177},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679169678,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":7756,"timeElapsed":330946},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679173532,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3852,"timeElapsed":334799},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679180823,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":7289,"timeElapsed":342091},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679184092,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3267,"timeElapsed":345360},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679206572,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":22478,"timeElapsed":367839},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679213581,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":7007,"timeElapsed":374849},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679218421,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":4837,"timeElapsed":379689},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679222092,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":3669,"timeElapsed":383360},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679230653,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"46","question":"Do you enjoy performing for others? In what ways?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":8560,"timeElapsed":391921},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679270608,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":37230,"timeElapsed":431876},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679275334,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":4724,"timeElapsed":436602},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679279417,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4081,"timeElapsed":440684},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679283389,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3970,"timeElapsed":444657},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679287716,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4326,"timeElapsed":448984},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679290792,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3073,"timeElapsed":452060},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679293943,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3149,"timeElapsed":455211},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679298093,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":4148,"timeElapsed":459361},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679302029,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3934,"timeElapsed":463297},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679311038,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":6626,"timeElapsed":472306},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679314677,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":3637,"timeElapsed":475945},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679319723,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":5044,"timeElapsed":480991},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679322558,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":2832,"timeElapsed":483826},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679332316,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":9756,"timeElapsed":493584},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679335106,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":2788,"timeElapsed":496374},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679339493,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":4385,"timeElapsed":500761},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679342846,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":3351,"timeElapsed":504114},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679347915,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":5068,"timeElapsed":509183},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679363654,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":13037,"timeElapsed":524922},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679367192,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":3536,"timeElapsed":528460},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679372130,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":4936,"timeElapsed":533398},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679382231,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":10098,"timeElapsed":543499},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679386961,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":4728,"timeElapsed":548229},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679391780,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":4816,"timeElapsed":553047},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679396783,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":5002,"timeElapsed":558051},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679399329,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2544,"timeElapsed":560597},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679403267,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":3936,"timeElapsed":564535},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679412069,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":6231,"timeElapsed":573337},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679417355,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":5284,"timeElapsed":578623},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679422247,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":4891,"timeElapsed":583515},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679424859,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":2610,"timeElapsed":586127},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679430816,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":5954,"timeElapsed":592084},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679433864,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":3046,"timeElapsed":595132},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679440170,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":6304,"timeElapsed":601438},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679459418,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":19246,"timeElapsed":620686},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679463809,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":4389,"timeElapsed":625077},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679468769,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":4959,"timeElapsed":630037},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679476009,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":5455,"timeElapsed":637277},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679478726,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2715,"timeElapsed":639994},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679483516,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":4788,"timeElapsed":644783},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679487033,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":3516,"timeElapsed":648301},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679490698,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":3663,"timeElapsed":651966},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679493459,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2759,"timeElapsed":654727},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679498448,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":4987,"timeElapsed":659716},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679503185,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":4734,"timeElapsed":664453},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679509394,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":6208,"timeElapsed":670662},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679522798,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":11048,"timeElapsed":684066},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679525602,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2802,"timeElapsed":686870},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679529134,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":3530,"timeElapsed":690402},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679531953,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":2818,"timeElapsed":693221},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679540523,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":8568,"timeElapsed":701791},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679543344,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":2819,"timeElapsed":704612},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679550863,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":7517,"timeElapsed":712131},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679555962,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":5098,"timeElapsed":717230},{"subjectID":"3vqss0kbgj","prolificID":"566feba6b937e400052d33b2","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b26def920529cec1276","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679567249,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":11285,"timeElapsed":728516}]